<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogging on John Cosio</title>
    <link>https://johncosio.com/tags/blogging.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogging on John Cosio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 13:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://johncosio.com/tags/blogging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Games that actually end</title>
      <link>https://johncosio.com/posts/2017/11/games-that-actually-end.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 13:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johncosio.com/posts/2017/11/games-that-actually-end.html</guid>
      <description>Well hello there! Got some new toys from humblebundle.com. Pretty good deal at $15 you get 7-8 games.
First time in a while playing some games that actually have and ending.
For some time I was into MMORPGs, DoTA, mobile games(Clash of Clans, Summoners War) but sometimes it&amp;#8217;s good to go back to basics.
Back in the day you play games until you see The End, Fin.
It was a really good feeling to watch the credits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ways to make money from your website</title>
      <link>https://johncosio.com/posts/2016/04/ways-to-make-money-from-your-website.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 07:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johncosio.com/posts/2016/04/ways-to-make-money-from-your-website.html</guid>
      <description>You can also make money from your website. While most of the time it is only used for displaying your products or your company information
We&amp;#8217;ll be talking on ways to get some cash back from just having a website online. Regarding how much and how big or small you get, your mileage may vary.
Back on topic now, Here comes my list:  Place advertisements This is a very common way to get some income, you only need to get an advertiser and place their ads on your website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On writing blog posts</title>
      <link>https://johncosio.com/posts/2016/04/on-writing-blog-posts.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 05:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johncosio.com/posts/2016/04/on-writing-blog-posts.html</guid>
      <description>When I started setting up my websites on wordpress.com and blogspot.com I have one goal in mind. To earn some extra MONEY. Yup that is correct, after reading so many articles, guides and tutorials on writing blog posts and making money from your blog; I decided to give it a try.
The problem is after having signing up with those blogging services and customizing how your site looks, you don&amp;#8217;t have anything on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How can we consider ourselves &amp;#8220;Experts&amp;#8221;</title>
      <link>https://johncosio.com/posts/2016/02/how-can-we-consider-ourselves-#8220experts%238221.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 04:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johncosio.com/posts/2016/02/how-can-we-consider-ourselves-#8220experts%238221.html</guid>
      <description>I was checking out some job openings at Upwork(WHICH I NEVER GET HIRED EVEN BEFORE WHEN IT WAS ODESK) and other freelance/job post sites. There were many people looking for &amp;#8220;Experts&amp;#8221;. WordPress Experts, Design Experts, SEO Experts, PHP Experts, Rockstar Designers blah blah blah.
Questions started to pop up one after another which I can&amp;#8217;t even answer. Am I an expert? I&amp;#8217;ve been customizing and building websites from some time but I can&amp;#8217;t consider myself an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So many games so little time: Plants vs Zombies</title>
      <link>https://johncosio.com/posts/2015/10/so-many-games-so-little-time-plants-vs-zombies.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 04:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johncosio.com/posts/2015/10/so-many-games-so-little-time-plants-vs-zombies.html</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&amp;#8217;ve decided to write about games I played. Sort of a review but not in-depth, there are many other sites that focus on that.
This time we&amp;#8217;ll be talking about Plants vs Zombies.
It came out around 2009 when I was still in college, some of my friends introduced me to it.
At first I found it weird. Usual tower defense games have the camera position on top but this is like playing Mario and other side scrolling games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world!</title>
      <link>https://johncosio.com/posts/2015/02/hello-world.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2015 07:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johncosio.com/posts/2015/02/hello-world.html</guid>
      <description>Hello! This is my first post. I used to have another blog and use this as my landing page but it is now inactive.
I&amp;#8217;ll be trying to use this from now on. I haven&amp;#8217;t really thought about what to write here. I just want to be able search myself correctly from Google results.
Maybe next time I&amp;#8217;ll land on the number one spot.
By the way I really like black backgrounds with shiny life stream like images from FF7.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>