<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on John Cosio</title>
    <link>https://johncosio.com/tags/marketing.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on John Cosio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 09:58:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://johncosio.com/tags/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jenni Epperson</title>
      <link>https://johncosio.com/projects/2017-03-13-jenni-epperson.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 09:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johncosio.com/projects/2017-03-13-jenni-epperson.html</guid>
      <description>My first project using WordPress and working with Dart back in September 2013. Developed a WordPress child theme of twentyeleven from an already designed HTML template.
Second redesign was around March of 2015. The new theme was a responsive theme with a request to add a survey to get user feedback. The survey is mandatory and needs to be finished first before viewers can access the content.
Redesign results shows that it engages more users to access the site especially those that are using mobile devices, better ways to improve the website by taking into account viewer feedback and demographics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fastrack Courier Services</title>
      <link>https://johncosio.com/projects/2017-03-12-fastrack-courier-services.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 12:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johncosio.com/projects/2017-03-12-fastrack-courier-services.html</guid>
      <description>Web administration and booking application for a fast growing logistics company. Involved in the overall improvement of their current system which deals with the system flow and the actual operation process.
Streamlined the booking and processing of bookings by filtering and reducing redundant bookings per day to only show unique records.
Updated the functionality to give a clear and straightforward process into using the website that results in a smoother user experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>