<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gundam Deathscythe-Hell EW on John Cosio</title>
    <link>https://johncosio.com/tags/gundam-deathscythe-hell-ew/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gundam Deathscythe-Hell EW on John Cosio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 12:39:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://johncosio.com/tags/gundam-deathscythe-hell-ew/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GIMP Complete: SD Gundam EX-Standard Gundam Deathscythe-Hell EW</title>
      <link>https://johncosio.com/posts/2019/04/gimp-complete-sd-gundam-ex-standard-gundam-deathscythe-hell-ew/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 12:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johncosio.com/posts/2019/04/gimp-complete-sd-gundam-ex-standard-gundam-deathscythe-hell-ew/</guid>
      <description>This is my first take on painting with GIMP.
Subject is the Gundam Deathscythe-Hell EW version.
Practicing adding glowing things to eyes and the scythe.
Before 
After 
I got some more posts coming up. Cleaning up the Gundam Crossbones and working on the SD Sinanju.
Still 2 more SD then moving on to my MG kit or get some HG for practice.
This is actually quite relaxing. Haven&amp;#8217;t opened Steam in a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Complete: SD Gundam EX-Standard Gundam Deathscythe-Hell EW</title>
      <link>https://johncosio.com/posts/2019/04/build-complete-sd-gundam-ex-standard-gundam-deathscythe-hell-ew/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 02:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johncosio.com/posts/2019/04/build-complete-sd-gundam-ex-standard-gundam-deathscythe-hell-ew/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve actually posted the edited version first in GIMP Complete
Model Kit: SD Gundam EX-Standard Gundam Deathscythe-Hell EW
I enjoy building these kits then posing them around then taking photos.
Figured I can edit them to add details then clean up nubs.
Picture time!                Tried editing the background out and replacing with space.
Space background image in edited photo by Alexander Andrews</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Hobby: Building little plastic Gundam models</title>
      <link>https://johncosio.com/posts/2019/04/new-hobby-building-little-plastic-gundam-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 02:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johncosio.com/posts/2019/04/new-hobby-building-little-plastic-gundam-models/</guid>
      <description>Some info Last week I got back from Japan. Write about Japan Trip here&amp;#8230; &amp;lt;- Future link
While I was there, the toys especially Gundam kits seems cheaper so I picked up a couple.
Built my first Gundam The first Gundam series I saw was Gundam Wing in our local channel GMA 7 when I was a kid.
Duo&amp;#8217;s Deathscythe was my favorite and was really lucky I got to pick this up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>